// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
  numb: 1,
  question: "Business correspondence is the communication or exchange of information in a written format for the process of business activities",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 2,
  question: "Business correspondence can only take place between organizations. ",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "Business correspondence is an informal communication",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
  question: "Business correspondence is all the written communication between the organization and its external and internal concerned parties.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "Business Memorandum can be classified as Internal Correspondence",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "E-Mails can be used in both external and internal correspondences.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "A notice is an oral statement that contains the particulars of holding any event in an organization. ",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "ASAP is an abbreviation for as soon as possible.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "AAM stands for automated teller machine.",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "C/A is a shortened form of the word ‘account’.",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: "External correspondence is with outsiders that include customers, suppliers, government agencies, other business houses and any other stakeholder.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
  question: "Internal correspondence is with the internal parties of the organization which is generally done with the employees.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 13,
  question: "- B2B is the abbreviation of Business to Business.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
  question: "B2C is the shortened form of Business to Consumer. ",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
  question: "Balance Sheet is the full form of B/S.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 16,
  question: "CEO is the abbreviation of Chief Executive Officer.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 17,
  question: "CV is the abbreviation of Curriculum Vitae.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 18,
  question: "Disc. is the abbreviation of Discount. ",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 19,
  question: "A/C is the shortened form of Current Account.",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 20,
  question: "E-Commerce is the abbreviation of Electronic Commerce.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 21,
  question: "- Etc. is the abbreviation of Et Cetera which means and other things.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 22,
  question: "e.g can be written in full form as Exempli gratia.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 23,
  question: "FIFO is the abbreviation of First-In-First-Out.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 24,
  question: "FYI is the abbreviation of For Your Information.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},  {
  numb: 25,
  question: "HQ is the shortened form of Head Quarters.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 26,
  question: "Traditional Marketing is the performance of business activities that direct the flow of goods and services from the producer to consumer or user.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 27,
  question: "Modern Marketing is the process of determining consumer demand for a product or service, motivating its sales and distributing it into ultimate consumption at a profit.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 28,
  question: "A marketing plan is a document which records the activities carried out by the marketing team. ",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 29,
  question: "A marketing plan is a necessary effort to start with before any marketing effort.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 30,
  question: "A marketing plan is a necessary effort to end with after any marketing effort",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 31,
  question: "A marketing plan is an unnecessary effort to start with before any marketing effort.",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb:32,
  question: "Market research is the process of evaluating the feasibility of a new product or service, through research conducted with potential consumers.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 33,
  question: "- Market research can be conducted directly by organizations or can be outsourced to agencies that have expertise in this process.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 34,
  question: "Market research can only be conducted directly by organizations or companies.",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 35,
  question: "Market research cannot be outsourced to agencies that have expertise in this process.",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 36,
  question: "- Brainstorming is the process of searching for ideas by taking every thought into consideration and transforming them into marketing decisions later. ",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 37,
  question: "Brainstorming can be group-wide and individual. ",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 38,
  question: "Brainstorming can only be group-wide and not individual. ",
  answer:"false",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 39,
  question: "Accounting has rightly been termed as the language of the business",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
  {
  numb: 40,
  question: "Accounting is the art of recording, classifying and summarizing financial transactions and events and interpreting the results thereof.",
  answer:"true",
  options: [
    "true",
    "false",
  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 1,
  question: " ……….. is the communication or exchange of information in a written format for the process of business activities.",
  answer:"Business Correspondence",
  options: [
    "Business Correspondence",
    "Corporation",
    "Business",
    "Mechine",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 2,
  question: "Business correspondence is a ……..communication.",
  answer:"formal",
  options: [
    "informal",
    "corporate",
    "formal",
    "intimate",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 3,
  question: "Business correspondence is all the …….. communication between the organization and its external and internal concerned parties.",
  answer:"written",
  options: [
    "spoken",
    "oral",
    "written",
    "electronic",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 4,
  question: " …… can be used in both external and internal correspondences.",
  answer:"E-mails",
  options: [
    "E-mails",
    "A Memorandum",
    "A notice",
    "A business letter",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 5,
  question: "The abbreviation of First-in-First-out is……",
  answer:"FIFO",
  options: [
    "FIFA",
    "FIFO",
    "LIFO",
    "FIOF",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 6,
  question: "Business memorandum is.....formal than e-mails.",
  answer:"more",
  options: [
    "more",
    "less",
    "same",
    "not",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Businsee Correspndence always.......",
  answer:"impersonal",
  options: [
    "informal",
    "external",
    "internal",
    "impersonal",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "A......is a written statment that contains the paticulars of holding any event in a organization.",
  answer:"Notice",
  options: [
    "Memo",
    "Letter",
    "Notice",
    "document",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "A notice is an example of …… correspondence.",
  answer:"internal",
  options: [
    "External",
    "personal",
    "oral",
    "internal",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "……. are known for being paperless, quick and cheap.",
  answer:"Emalis",
  options: [
    "Business letter",
    "Memorandum",
    "Emalis",
    "Notice",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 11,
  question: "E-mails are……..formal than Business letters.",
  answer:"less",
  options: [
    "more",
    "less",
    "same",
    "not",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 12,
  question: "The abbreviation of current account is…..",
  answer:"C/A",
  options: [
    "A/C",
    "CC",
    "C/A",
    "AA",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 13,
  question: "………correspondence is with the internal parties of the organization which is generally done with the employees.",
  answer:"internal",
  options: [
    "internal",
    "external",
    "informal",
    "international",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 14,
  question: " ……correspondence is usually done with outsiders that include customers, suppliers, etc.",
  answer:"External",
  options: [
    "External",
    "informal",
    "international",
    "internal",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 15,
  question: "As soon  as possible is the full form of ......",
  answer:"ASAP",
  options: [
    "AASP",
    "ASAP",
    "APAS",
    "SPAA",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 16,
  question: "discount can be abbrevited as.......",
  answer:"disc.",
  options: [
    "Dsc",
    "disc.",
    "desc",
    "dsic.",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 17,
  question: "internal business correspondance is usually done by......",
  answer:"employees",
  options: [
    "customers",
    "employees",
    "outsiders",
    "suppliers",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 18,
  question: "Business letters and emails can be classified as.......correspondence.",
  answer:"external",
  options: [
    "quick",
    "external",
    "internal",
    "personal",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 19,
  question: "-Memos, emails and notices can be classified as........correspondence",
  answer:"internal",
  options: [
    "informal",
    "external",
    "internal",
    "personal",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 20,
  question: "A...... is an example of business correspondence with outsiders that takes time and uses paper.",
  answer:"business letter",
  options: [
    "emails",
    "business letter",
    "memo",
    "notice",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 21,
  question: "The shortened form of Balance Sheet is......",
  answer:"B/S",
  options: [
    "PS",
    "SP",
    "B/S",
    "S/B",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb:22,
  question: "The opposite of FIFO which means First-in-First-out is……",
  answer:"LIFO",
  options: [
    "FIFA",
    "FIFO",
    "LIFO",
    "FIOF",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 23,
  question: "The Latin meaning of e.g, which means for example, is.....",
  answer:"exempli gratia",
  options: [
    "exempli gratia",
    "exempli great",
    "gratia exempli-",
    "gratia example",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 24,
  question: "The Latin meaning of etc, which means and other things, is......",
  answer:"et cetera",
  options: [
    "et cetera",
    "cetera et",
    "eat cetera",
    "cetera eat",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 25,
  question: "-A notice is a form of ……communication.",
  answer:"downward",
  options: [
    "upward",
    "external",
    "downward",
    "personal",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 26,
  question: "The balance sheet, also known as………, shows a business‘s assets, liabilities, and equity at a point in time.",
  answer:"Statement of financial position",
  options: [
    "Statement of financial position",
    "Income statement",
    "Cost statement",
    "Ledger",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 27,
  question: "…….. shows a business‘s assets, liabilities, and equity at a point in time.",
  answer:"The balance sheet",
  options: [
    "The balance sheet",
    "Income statement",
    "Cost statement",
    "Ledger",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 28,
  question: "Assets= Liabilities + ....... .",
  answer:" Owner’s Equity",
  options: [
    " Owner’s Equity",
    "Expenses",
    "Net income",
    "Revenues",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 29,
  question: "Owner’s Equity = ……….. ـــ Liabilities",
  answer:"Assets",
  options: [
    "Assets",
    "Revenues",
    "Expenses",
    "Net income",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb:32,
  question: "An ……..communicates information about a business‘s financial performance by summarizing revenues less expenses over a period of time.",
  answer:"income statement",
  options: [
    "income statement",
    "The balance sheet",
    "Ledger",
    "Cost statement",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 33,
  question: " ………….. = Revenues - Expenses.",
  answer:"Net Income",
  options: [
    "Net Income",
    "Assets",
    "Liabilities",
    "Owner’s Equity",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 34,
  question: "Revenues= ……….. + Expenses.",
  answer:"Net Income",
  options: [
    "Net Income",
    "Assets",
    "Liabilities",
    "Owner’s Equity",

  
  
  ]
},

{
  numb: 37,
  question: " ………. is the management of company personnel through the staffing functions which include planning, recruitment, selection, orientation, training, performance appraisal, compensation, and safety",
  answer:"Human Resource Management",
  options: [
    "Human Resource Management",
    "Recruitment",
    "Performance Appraisal",
    "Orientation",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 38,
  question: "……… is the process of choosing the best candidate among the candidates applied for the job.",
  answer:"Selection",
  options: [
    "Selection",
    "Recruitment",
    "Compensation",
    "Performance Appraisal",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 39,
  question: "- ……. is a formal system of review and evaluation of individual or team task performance.",
  answer:"Performance Evaluation (Appraisal)",
  options: [
    "Performance Evaluation (Appraisal)",
    "Orientation",
    "Recruitment",
    "Compensation",

  
  
  ]
},
{
  numb: 40,
  question: "……. means the advancement of an employee to a higher job involving more work, greater responsibility and higher status.",
  answer:"Promotion",
  options: [
    "Promotion",
    "Selection",
    "Motivation",
    "Recruitment",

  
  
  ]
},
];

// Shuffle questions array
questions.sort(function() {
  return 0.5 - Math.random();
});



// Select the first 30 questions
questions = questions.slice(0, 30);

